frank151.com 2019-04-01

# Frank151 Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is applies to <http://www.frank151.com/>, and any other site that may be operated by or for F151 Ventures, LLC (together, the "Websites"). It explains how we collect information from users of the Websites and how we use such information. Your use of the Websites constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. Please also read our Term of Use, which govern the basic operation of the Websites.  If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, you should immediately stop using or visiting the Websites.

**1\. The Information We Collect and Use**

A. Non-Personally Identifiable Information. When you visit a Website, we may collect certain data that does not tell us specifically who you are. This is “Non-Personally Identifiable Information.” It includes things like your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, and the last domain you visited before coming to our Website or the domain you go to when you leave. It also includes various statistical data such as which pages you visit on our Websites, how long you stay on them, and what you click.

We may place a “cookie” on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Our “preference” cookie expires after thirty (30) days. We may use cookies to keep track of your choice of language and home page preference; to understand your exposure to certain Internet advertisements as you use the Websites, and to gather usage data that will help us generally improve the quality of the Websites. There is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept cookies. You should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with certain features on the Websites.

We also may use a small piece of code (sometimes referred to as “1x1 clear pixel,” “Web beacon” or “clear GIF”) placed in the pages of the Websites to help us gather additional information about which parts of the site receive the most visitors and other user traffic patterns, and enable us to administer the site.

No Personally Identifiable Information (see below) is collected through our cookies or Web beacons however we may, from time to time, allow advertisers, third-party advertising networks, and third-party advertising serving companies to serve advertisements directly to you within our Websites, Services, and Software.  By serving these advertisements directly to you, these companies can set their own cookies on your computer, which may not expire, and trigger their own Web beacons.  If you would like to contact the advertisers, third-party advertising networks, and third-party advertising serving companies with which we have relationships to learn more about their privacy policies and what options (if any) they offer to opt out of their data collection, please visit their web sites.   Some of these companies are participants in the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”), a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards.  You can learn more about NAI and how you may “opt out” of targeted advertising delivered by NAI member ad networks at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

B. Personally Identifiable Information. We also may collect information that can be used to identify you (“Personally Identifiable Information”). We only collect Personally Identifiable Information when you specifically provide it to us. For example, in connection with your subscription to or use of certain features of the Websites you may be asked to create a user account and provide certain information including your name, email addresses, address, and telephone number. You may also provide User Uploaded Information to the Websites, as described in the Terms of Use, or you may provide information such as your credit card number in connection with the purchase of services or content available through the Websites. When you create a user account and sign in to your account on the Websites or post User Uploaded Information, you are not anonymous to us.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information to fulfill your requests, respond to your inquiries and provide other services, and to alert you to information, offers, or publications in which we think you may be interested. The emails that we send contain links that enable you to “unsubscribe” from such mailings.

We do not sell Personally Identifiable Information or other information you make available to the Websites, or share such information with third parties, except as described below.

From time to time, we may partner with unaffiliated companies or individuals for market research, product development or similar purposes. These companies or individuals may be provided with access to Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information, but we will require by contract that they agree to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of such information. We also may subcontract with other companies and individuals to do work on our behalf; they may be provided with access to Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information, but only as needed to perform their functions.

We may share Personally Identifiable Information with third parties, who may contact you to offer products and services. At any time, you can contact F151 Ventures, LLC at info@frank151.com to request that we not share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties.

We may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties in connection with a corporate transaction where all or a portion of our business (e.g., a portion that includes our customer lists) is sold or transferred. We also may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information if disclosure is required by law or as part of a lawsuit or government investigation or proceeding, or in order to permit us to exercise or preserve our legal rights or take action regarding potentially illegal activities or to protect the safety of any person.

We reserve the right, but have no obligation, to monitor information, comments or other content that you voluntarily disclose and post to the Websites. We reserve the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason, including without limitation, if in our sole opinion such information or material violates, or may violate, any applicable law or the Terms of Use or to protect or defend our rights or property or those of any third party. We also reserve the right to remove information upon the request of any third party.

We reserve the right to investigate abuses on the Websites and enforce and apply this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use and any other terms or conditions applicable to the Websites or the use thereof. We may disclose information about you to third parties if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (1) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (2) enforce or apply the Terms of Use; (3) comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding or other legal process served on us; (4) protect our rights, reputation, and property or that of our users or the public or (5) protect against legal liability.

**2\. Data Security**

We cannot ensure or warrant the security or privacy of any information you transmit to us. We attempt to follow policies and procedures that will protect against unauthorized access to your Personally Identifiable Information. But we can make no guarantees or promises in this regard, and you provide information to us at your own risk.

We may store the Personally Identifiable Information we hold about you indefinitely. We may store this information in the United States or we may transfer it to any other country. The data protection laws of the countries where we store your personal data may or may not provide a level of protection equivalent to the laws in your home country. Wherever we hold the data, we will apply the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**3\. Children**

This site is not directed at children under the age of 13 and we endeavor not to knowingly collect any Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that this site has collected the Personally Identifiable Information of a child under the age of 13, please contact [info@frank151.com](mailto:info@frank151.com)

**4\. Access to your information**

You may contact us at info@frank151.com if at any time you would like to see the Personally Identifiable Information we hold about you, or to ask us to correct or update this information, or to ask us to delete it. Please contact us if you have questions or wish to take any action with respect to information to which this Privacy Policy applies (see below for contact information).

**5\. Links to Other Websites**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Websites. The Websites may contain links to other websites that we may not own or operate. The links from the Websites do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed these websites. The policies and procedures we describe here do not apply to these websites. We neither can control nor are responsible for the privacy practices or content of these websites. We suggest contacting these websites directly for information on their privacy policies.

**6\. How To Contact Us**

You may contact F151 Ventures, LLC regarding our privacy practices at the following address:  
F151 Ventures LLC  
306 W. 38th Street  
New York, NY 10018

**7\. Changes To The Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 1, 2019. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We do not undertake to provide you with personal notice of any changes. In the event of material changes, we will provide notice by means that are reasonable under the circumstances, such as by posting a notice on the Websites. Your continued use of the Websites following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy means you accept those changes.
